<resources>
    <string name="app_name">CET Bhubaneswar</string>
    <string name="about_cet">The College of Engineering and Technology, Bhubaneswar was established by the Government of Odisha in 1981.
        It was a Constituent College of the Odisha University of Agriculture and Technology, Bhubaneswar since inception.
        After creation of a Technical University for Odisha State, the College has become a Constituent College of Biju Patnaik University of Technology (BPUT), Odisha with effect from 09th July, 2002 as per section-37(1) of BPUT Act, 2002.
        The College offers a five-year Under Graduate degree courses in Architecture (B.Arch.) and four-years B.Tech. degree in Biotechnology, Civil Engineering, Computer Science and Engineering, Electrical Engineering, Fashion and Apparel Technology,
        Information Technology, Instrumentation and Electronics Engineering, Mechanical Engineering and Textile Engineering. A three year Post Graduate course, Master in Computer Application (MCA) is also offered.
        In addition to the above courses M.Tech. courses in Structural Engineering (in the Department of Civil Engineering), Computer Science and Engineering, Information Technology and Industrial Engineering and Management (in Mechanical Engineering Department) have been running from Academic Year 2005-06.
        Master degree programme in Architecture i.e. M.Arch. has been running from the academic session 2007-08.
    </string>
    <string name="message">College of Engineering and Technology has been a pool of meritorious students consistently for many years.
        And hence it has always tried to facilitate quality engineering education to equip and enrich young men and women to meet global challenges in development, innovation and application of technology in the service of humanity.
        I would like to acknowledge the students for their consistent hard work due to which this college has been able to become the first and foremost choice of the aspiring engineers of Odisha.
        Let me also at the same time acknowledge the great alumni power, the present and the past faculty members of the institution who have built up this institution to high acclaim.
    </string>
    <string name="vision">To emerge as a global leader in Technical Education</string>
    <string name="mission">To generate on a sustainable basis quality technical human resources commensurate with the dynamic global scenario
    </string>
    <string name="attribute">"    \u2022 Engineering knowledge
    \u2022 Problem analysis
    \u2022 Design and Development of Solutions
    \u2022 Investigation of Complex Problem
    \u2022 Modern tool usage
    \u2022 Engineer and society
    \u2022 Environment and sustainability
    \u2022 Ethics
    \u2022 Individual and team work
    \u2022 Communication
    \u2022 Lifelong learning
    \u2022 Project management and finance"</string>
</resources>
